[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One angstrom unit equal what length in meters?", "correct_answer": "0.0000000001 meters", "incorrect_answers": ["0.000001 meters", "1,000,000,000 meters", "0.001 meters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US President was born in South Carolina although he lived in Tennessee when he became president.", "correct_answer": "Andrew Jackson", "incorrect_answers": ["William Henry Harrison", "Zachary Taylor", "Jimmy Carter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Like most mammals lions can only breed with one male ensuring that the offspring belong to just one male.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 3:10 to Yuma, how much money does Charlie Prince offer to anyone who shoots any member of the posse?", "correct_answer": "200 dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["1000 dollars", "100 dollars", "500 dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bloomsday is a secular holiday, which commemorates the life of Irish writer James Joyce and the fictitious events in his novel Ulysses. Bloomsday is celebrated annually, on what date?", "correct_answer": "June 16", "incorrect_answers": ["October 19", "December 24", "July 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Lightning McQueens truck in the film Cars?", "correct_answer": "Mack", "incorrect_answers": ["Chevy", "Red", "Peterbuilt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the James Bond movie You Only Live Twice, what is the name of the single-seat helicopter devised by gadget wizard Q, which manages to out-muscle opponents despite being outnumbered?", "correct_answer": "Little Nellie", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Gaby", "Little Suzie", "Little Daisy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the correct atomic number of the chemical element Actinium?", "correct_answer": "89", "incorrect_answers": ["99", "79", "78"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Sussex, England, the Ecopod Company uses recycled paper to make these.", "correct_answer": "Coffins", "incorrect_answers": ["Food canisters", "Apartments", "Dog houses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Bronte sisters wrote only one novel, which was published under the pseudonym Ellis Bell?", "correct_answer": "Emily", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlotte and Emily", "Charlotte", "Anne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the capybara, the largest rodent on the planet, indigenous to South America?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Its front legs are a little longer than the rear legs.", "It has 16 teeth.", "It has a short tail."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the villains mistress killed in the 1974 movie The Man with the Golden Gun?", "correct_answer": "At a kickboxing  match", "incorrect_answers": ["At a wrestling match", "At a tennis match", "At a judo match"]}]